The goal in this video isto display the details for
本视频的目的是为了展示
the comic book thatwas clicked on.
点击comic book后的细节
So let's go ahead andget started.
接下来我们开始吧
We'll do a couple of otherthings as well in this video.
本视频中，我们还会完成其他几个任务
The first thing I wannado is to lay out that
第一件事
grid that willcontain the details.
我想要对包含细节的Grid布局
So, I'm gonna take a momenthere and do some formatting.
因此我要在这里花点时间，来做一些格式调整
So commenting,
添加注释
so that I can easily findwhat I'm looking for.
这样我就能轻松地找到我要的内容了
Because things are starting toget a little bit hectic here.
这是到了，这里的任务会开始有一些繁琐
So this will be
所以这里将会是
the character detail.
角色的细节
And then this would bethe the Detail Grid.
这里是将会是细节的Grid
All right,that should help a little bit.
好了，这应该能帮上忙
Right, so under Comic Detailswe're gonna add another grid.
好的，我们现在在 Comic Details 这里添加了另一个 Grid
We're gonna put thisgrid in the third row.
我们现在要把Grid放在第三行
Remember, we created three rows,and
记住，我们创建了三行
this is going to the last one,
而且这个是最后一行
and we'll just go ahead andset all of this.
然后我们就可以继续设置所有的内容了
All right, and inside of thisgrid, I'm going to create pretty
好得，类似于上次我们为Character Details所做的工作
much like what we did last timewhere we had for the character
我们现在重新创建一个
detail, we had the definitionsfor columns and rows.
我们定义好行和列
I'm just gonna copy that exactlyand reuse it here with Comics.
我只要将上次的重新复制粘贴，在这里重用一次就好了
And I see I've alreadymade a mistake here.
哦，我们这里出现了一个失误
There we go.
继续
Nice.
没问题
All right, andthen inside of here,
好的，然后在这内部
I'm going to create prettymuch like what I did here.
我们要创建的东西就和上面这些差不多了
In fact, let me just goahead and grab this.
现在让我们继续复制它
And I wanna paste it.
接下来粘贴这部分
And here we're gonna go,instead of just DetailImages,
接下来呢，要把Detail Images改成
it will be ComicDetailImages.
Comic Detail Images
Instead of DetailName,it'll be ComicDetailNames.
Detail Name改成Comic Detail Names
Instead of DetailDescription,
DetailDescription改成
it'll beComicDetailDescriptionTextBlock.
ComicDetailDescriptionTextBlock
It's easy enough.
很轻松哈
All righty, and now,
好的
what I wanna do is lookat this List of Comics.
现在我要做的就是观察这一列Comics
Currently, I didn't givethe GridView and name before I
目前我没有为GridView任何名称
created the item click,I'm going to give it a name now.
现在我要为它编写一个
And we're going to call this,ComicsGridView.
我要把它叫做ComicGridView
And so, this should bethe ComicsGridView_ItemClick.
因此这个要命名为ComicGridView_ItemClick
And inside onthe MainPage.xml.cs,
在MainPage.xml.cs里面
let's rename this toComicsGridview_ItemClick.
我们把它重命名为ComicsGridview_ItemClick
So, in this what we're gonnado is essentially exactly what
好的，我们接下来要做的是
we did here where wegrabbed off the item and
在这个地方
then we startedpopulating things.
复制粘贴这段代码，然后开始生成内容        （审核注：这里应该是指调用 api）
So let's go ahead and justcopy that code, paste it here.
我们继续复制粘贴代码
And we're gonnachange everything up
接下来我们要
from Character to Comic.
把每个 Character 更换为 Comic
ComicBook.
ComicBook.
selectedComic.
selectedComic.
And the comic has a title,not a name.
comic 应该有个标题而不是名字
So we'll change that.
因此我们要修改这里
Otherwise, everything willbe just about correct.
这样的话所有的问题都解决了
Let's make sure we'resetting ComicDetailName in
确认一下我们已经在 ComicDetailDescription 中
ComicDetailDescription.
重新设置好了 ComicDetailName
All right.
好的
Let's run it, see if it works.
运行起来，看看是否能工作
Okay, and eventually we gotit to completely fill in.
好的，最后我们完全实现并且替换了内容
Awesome.
厉害
We'll select Crimson Dynamo.
我们选择 Crimson Dynamo
Great.
真棒
And I'm gonna select one ofthe items, like that comic.
我要选择其中一个内容，比如这个 comic
Okay, you can see thatwe do see the details,
好的，现在你可以看到实现的细节
but I have to basically resizethe window so I can get to it.
但是我要改变窗口大小，这样才能够到
There's no Scroll viewer.
这儿没有 Scoll Viewer
So let's change that.
好的，接下来开始修改吧
Let's go back tothe MainPage.xml and I add
我们回到 MainPage.xml
a outermost grid,inside of that a scroll viewer.
然后我要在外面添加一个 Grid
So here I'm gonna go Grid andthen ScrollViewer.
因此在这里我要先添加 Grid 然后 ScrollViewer
Like that.
就像这样
And then,I'm gonna just grab everything
接下来我要剪切写好的这部分代码
that we've previously done,cut it, and paste it in.
然后粘贴
And the reason I'mdoing it this way is
这么做可以保证
because then the indentationwill be right.
换行和间隔是正确的
If we just tried to wrapthe grid and scroll viewer
我们我们想在现有的代码基础上收缩 grid 与 scroll viewer
around the existing code,it doesn't work as well.
它也无法起作用
I've found in myunfortunate experiences.
这些都曾经存在我的不幸开发经历中
All right.
好的
Fin Fang Foom,interesting character.
Fin Fang Foom, 有意思的角色
And let's choose one of thecomics and we can see whoops.
接下来我们选择其中一个 comic 然后就可以看到了
Okay, now what do we have here?
好的，那么现在我们有什么了
All right, in this case thedescription is actually null.
没错，现在了 description 部分实际上是 null 的
So maybe we need todo a check for that.
那么我们要检查一遍原因
Okay great, try that again.
好的，再试一次
And this is why you wanna test,and test, and test, and keep
这就是你为什么要测试、测试然后一直运行应用的理由
running the application, keepusing it, because eventually,
随着你使用的越来越久
You're gonna find new, and
你会发现更多的新颖
interesting problemswith the application.
有趣的问题
The more you test it the morestable it'll be eventually.
你测试的越多，应用就会更加的稳定.
Okay, now I just discovereda bug if you noticed that.
好的，你注意到我刚才已经发现了一个 BUG
Previously, we had selecteda comic and displayed it here.
以前我们选择 comic 然后在这里展示
And then I selecteda new character.
然后我们选择一个新的 character , comicbooks 发生了改变
The comicbooks changed, butas you can see, without making
但是正如你所看到的
a selection, all of the previousdata is still here.
如果不做一个选择，所有以前的数据不会消失
So what we'll need todo is add a little
所以我们要做的就是
bit of logic right here whereyou click on a given new person.
为点击新人物的事件添加一些逻辑
So, I don't know where wecan put that it doesn't
我现在不知道我们应该在哪里放它
really matter, here we'll putit right here this is fine.
但这没关系，放这里就好了
So we move the comicdetail description
现在我们那移动comicdetail描述设置
setting that to empty string ComicDetailMainTextBlock.Test
来令ComicDetailMainTextBlock.Test
equals empty string.
为空字符
And then we'll goComicDetailImage and
接下来我们移动到goComicDetailImage
we'll set its sourceequal to null.
然后将source设置为null
Let's see if that works.
接下来看能否成功
Just curious what happens,while we're still loading this,
如果我能点击的话
if I can click on that.
我很感兴趣导入的时候发生了什么
And I can.
我真的可以
And that's the beauty of async.
这就是异步操作的美妙之处了
All right, so we've selecteda comic from Giant Man,
好的，我们已经从 Giant Man 中选择了 Comic
and I'm going to changeto a different character.
接下来我们要转移到另一个 character 上
And all the details about thatcomic go away, as well the list
现在所有关于 comic 的 details 都已经消失了
of comics for the previouscharacter for Giant Man.
以及一系列 Giant Man 曾经的角色
All right, perfect.
好的，完美了
Click Goliath.
点击 Goliath
All right, let's choose comic,beautiful.
好的，我们选择comic
Okay, very good.
好的，很棒
The last thing I'dwant to do is,
最后我要做的是，像之前我们为
I'm considering doing somethinglike this that we did earlier
comic books 的 character 所做的一样
for the characters forcomic books.
做一个同样的功能
I'm just not sureif it's necessary.
但我不确定这是否必要
Boy, it's a hard call,where do we make that call in?
这是个很麻烦的调用，我不记得在哪里调的
Yeah we make it right thereI guess it wouldn't hurt.
对，没问题，我觉得没什么影响
Let's do this.
我们开始吧
Going to copy it, more fora template than anything else.
复制，需要更多的模板
And what we'll dois grab this off,
接下来我们要做的就是把复制这部分代码
enter that there andchange that to Comics.
将它粘贴到这里然后更改为Comics
Let's move
我们稍微
this guy over a little bit,move that guy over a little bit.
移动一下这一部分
And we'll remove that.
删掉这部分代码
So this should ensure that weget ten comics, if they exist.
好的，这下就能保证我们能获得十个comic，如果有的话
Now, if they don't exist.
现在，如果不存在
Hm, see this is where thingsget a little bit tricky.
嗯，看起来事情有些让人摸不着头脑了
See, I know in this case thatthere are 1,500 characters.
看到，我知道在这个情况下，有超过1500个角色
What I don't know is that ifevery single character has at
我不知道的是
least ten comic booksassociated with it.
如果每个角色都有超过十个comic book相关
It may have zero.
它有可能是零
But there would be no wayto really figure that out,
但是如果不传递以前的一些信息，比如账号
Without passing back some pieceof information, like account.
我们没办法解决这个问题
So, I'm going to backtrackaway from this idea.
因此我要从这个思路中回溯一下
You can experiment withthis if you'd like.
当然如果你想的话也可以实验一下
But, the danger is,
但是现在的危险是
that you would end up makingan unlimited number of calls.
你会陷入到无尽的调用之中
Returning back the samecount of one or
如果你只返回相同数目或者一到两个comic
two comics, andyou wouldn't want to do that.
这个问题就不会发生
You would use up all thousandof your requests in about ten
你会在约10秒钟内花光成千上万个请求
So we're gonna go back or I'llleave that code commented out so
所以我要回过头去看那些注释的代码
that you can maybe think aboutsome alternative strategies that
这样我才有可能想出一些其他可行的策略
allow you to filterout the exceptions,
来允许你过滤掉这些异常
make sure that an exceptiondidn't happen.
保证异常不会发生
Maybe that's all we needto do here actually.
也许这就是我们要做的全部内容了
We'll just do this.
这就是我们的工作
Okay, we'll leave it at that.
我们先暂时停止改动
All right, so that's all thatI wanted to do in this lesson.
好的，这就是今天课堂的要讲的内容了
I'm pretty happywhere things are at.
我很高兴今天的成果
The next thing I want to dois add an adaptive layout so
接下来我就要添加一个适应性的布局
that we can resize andthings look good.
从而我们可以重新改变大小而有更好的外观
So we'll do thatin the next video.
下个视频我们就要讲这些内容
See you there, thanks.
下次再见，谢谢